Guide to the Kristine Stiles Collection, 1900-[ongoing] RL.01254
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Name files, 42 boxes
  - Valentino, Erin, 2000 (Box 199)
  - Van der Heide, Be, 1978 (Box 199)
  - Van Miegroet, Hans, 2007 (Box 199)
  - Vancouver Art Gallery, 2003 (Box 199)
  - Vautier, Ben, 1999 (Box 199)
  - Verlan, Mark, 2008 (Box 200)
  - Vesna, Victoria (Box 200)
  - Vickers, Amy, 1994-1998 (Box 200)
  - Vieille, Paul, 1993 (Box 200)
  - Vinanti, Marissa, 2009 (Box 200)
  - Vineri, vol. 2 no. 5 (Box 200)
  - Virus Virus! (Box 200)
  - Visser, Matthias, 1993-1995 (Box 200)
  - Viswanathan, Prabha (Box 200)
  - Vital, no. 1-6 (Box 200)
  - Vorhoff Merritt, Ariel (Box 200)
  - Voros, David, 2002 (Box 200)
  - Waanders, Hans, 1997 (Box 200)
  - Wagner, Anne M., 1993 (Box 200)
  - Wald, Priscilla, 2004 (Box 200)
  - Walker, John A., 1994-1996 (Box 200)
  - Walker, Julia A., 2004-2014 (Box 200)
  - Walker, Kara, 2007-2008 (Box 200)
  - Walker, Le Nitra (Box 200)
  - Wang, Jing, 2000 (Box 200)
  - Ward, Frazer, 2009 (Box 200)
  - Warr, Tracey, 2002 (Box 200)
  - Waschmaschine Galerie, 1999 (Box 200)
  - Wassink, Sonds Murray (Box 200)
  - Waters, John (Box 200)
  - Waterston, Darren, 1998 (Box 200)
  - Watkin, Mel, 1990-1997 (Box 200)
  - Watkins, Brad, 1995 (Box 200)
  - Watley, Louanne, 2001 (Box 200)
  - Waugh, Ishbel, 1997 (Box 200)
  - Way, Andrea, 1989-2012 (Box 200)
  - Wayman, Adele, 1994 (Box 200)
  - Wayne, Shoshana, 1999-2003 (Box 201)
  - Weaver, Katherine (Box 201)
  - Webb, Sarah, 1999-2001 (Box 201)
  - Weems, Carrie Mae, 1993-2014 (Box 201)
  - Wehrenberg, Charles and Larsen, Sally (Box 201, Box 214)
  - Weibel, Peter (Box 201)
  - Weiner, Lawrence, 1979-2009 (Box 201)
  - Weisman, Doreen, 1987 (Box 201)
  - Welly, Catherine (Box 201)
  - West, Franz, 2003 (Box 201)
  - West, Jessica B., 2007 (Box 201)
  - Wharton, Annabel, 2000 (Box 201)
  - Whiteside, Tom (Box 201)
  - White, Amy, 2007 (Box 201)
  - White, Lili (Box 201)
  - Whiting, Jim (Box 201)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1998 (Box 201)
  - WHO Media Art Biennale (Box 214)
  - Whitney, Martha (Box 201)
  - Wild, Thomas, 2008 (Box 201)
  - Wilding, Faith, 2001 (Box 201)
  - Wilhite, Alex, 2000 (Box 201)
  - Wilke, Hannah, 1994 (Box 201)
  - Willats, Stephen, 1991-1992 (Box 201)
  - Williams, Emmett, 2002 (Box 201)
  - Williams, Lyneise, 2006-2009 (Box 201)
  - Williams, Reese (Box 201)
  - Williams, Sheldon, 1978 (Box 201)
  - Wilson, Andrew (Box 202)
  - Wilson, Karen, University of Chicago Press (Box 202)
  - Wilson, Fred, 2004 (Box 202)
  - Wilson, Louise K., 2000 (Box 202)
  - Wilson, Martha, 2000 (Box 202)
  - Wilson, Sarah, 1998 (Box 202)
  - Winner, Chrisopher P., 1994 (Box 202)
  - Winters, Terry, 1991 (Box 202)
  - Withers, Josephine, 1995 (Box 202)
  - Wharton-Little, Glenda, 1991 (Box 202)
  - Winarsky, Hanne, 2008 (Box 202)
  - Winterstern, Salina, 1986 (Box 202)
  - Wired Magazine (Box 202)
  - Wissoker, Ken, 2007 (Box 202)
  - Wolff, Janet, 1997 (Box 202)
  - Wolffer, Lorena, 1997 (Box 202)
  - Wood, Christopher, 2005 (Box 202)
  - Wood, Denis (Box 202)
  - Woodall, John, 1988 (Box 202)
  - Woodard, Bill, 1991 (Box 202)
  - Woolf, Jamie (Box 202)
  - Workman, John, 2008-2011 (Box 202)
  - Works in Space (Box 202)
  - WRO Art Center (Box 202, Box 214)
  - Yeh, Gary, 2015 (Box 214)
  - WRO Foundation, 1999 (Box 202)
  - Yoldas, Pinar (Box 202)
  - Yoshihide, Otomo, 2010 (Box 202)
  - Yoshimoto, Midori, 2003 (Box 202)
  - Yugoslavia (Box 202)
  - Zabala, Gabriela, 2009 (Box 202)
  - Zazeela, Marian (Box 202)
  - Zemel, Carol, 1991 (Box 202)
  - Ziegler, Mel, 1999 (Box 202)
  - Zimmerli, Embodied Memories: The Work of Trauma in Art, 2011 (Box 202)
  - Zinn, Douglas (Box 202)
  - Ziolkowska, Magdelena, 2008 (Box 202)
  - Zucker, Sara, 2006 (Box 202)
  - Zwietnig, Paul Rotterdam (Box 202)
  - Miscellaneous or Unknown (Box 202)
  - Kelly, Dr. James R. (Box 214)
  - Krukowski, Samantha (Box 214)
  - Kutnick, Aaron (Box 214)
  - Lee, Young Ji (Box 214)
  - Le Lann, Gerard (Box 214)
  - Lozier, Susan (Box 214)
  - McDonough, Kaye (Kathryn) (Box 215)
  - McWilliam, Neil (Box 214)
  - Mahtaney, Sujata (Box 214)
  - Mims, Nancy (Box 214)
  - Munchner Kammerspiele (Box 214)
  - Ernst, Rhys and Drucker, Zackary (Box 214)
  - Purcell, Wendy (Box 214)
  - Civil Counter-Reconnaissance, Vienna (Box 214)
  - Cambodia, Season of a Living Arts Festival (Box 214)
  - LIVE: Biennial of Performance Art (Box 214)
  - Stemberger, Claudia Marion (Box 214)
  - Samy, Jacqueline (Box 214)
  - Institute for New Culture Technologies, World Information Institute (Box 214)
  - Magazyn Luxus, Wroclaw, Powland (Box 214)
  - Mansfield, Elizabeth (Cassie) (Box 214)
  - Russell, Clark, ca. 1983 (Box 214)
  - Shapiro, Elijah (Box 214)
- Audiovisual materials, 5 boxes
  Videotapes and recordings, many sent to Stiles by artists promoting their work. Also includes interviews of Raphael Montañez Ortiz.
  - Audiovisual materials (Box 165-168)
  - Interviews of Raphael Montañez Ortiz (Box 177)
  - REPORT by Bruce Conner, 1967
    Print of Bruce Conner's 1967 film, REPORT. Original can label contains the designation "(two)" after the title. 500 feet, approximately 13 minutes.
    - Original 16mm motion picture print (Box 229, Film-reel RL01254-F16-0001)
  - "Collecting the Future" presentation at Artpool 40 - Active Archives and Art Networks conference, 2020; One file; approximately 100 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0001)
    Video file in MP4 format.
- Other artist writings, 1 box
  Copies of articles and writings given to Stiles by other artists.
  - Ortiz, Raphael Montañez (Box 170)
  - Lerager, James (Box 170)
  - Schneeman, Carolee (Box 170)
  - Harrison (Box 170)
- Posters and oversize materials, 7 boxes, 12 tubes, and 4 oversize folders
  Oversize posters, handbills, photographs, artwork, etc.
  - Fredrica Drotos photographs, taken with a Hasleblatt camera (Box 179)
    - Robert Seidler, 1984 (Box 179)
    - Robert Seidler Band, 1984 (Box 179)
    - Punk, no date (Box 179)
  - Club Foot poster, designed by J.C. Garrett for the Alter Boys and Club Foot album, circa 1980 (Oversize-folder 5)
  - Hervé Fischer materials
    - 2 posters of Jordaners. Maak uw krant and the newspaper Het Parool in Amsterdam, 1978 (Oversize-folder 5)
    - 1 poster and handbills from Comment imaginez-vous l'avenir?, a project undertaken in Guebwiller, Alsace, France, by the Group de l'art sociologique, 1978 August 26-September 1. (Oversize-folder 5)
    - 2 folders of newspapers published as a result of the Comment imaginez-vous l'avenir? project (Oversize-folder 5)
    - Citoyens / Sculpteurs project, 1980 (Oversize-folder 5)
    - ?Que es la Sociodad Mexicana?, 1982 (Oversize-folder 5)
  - Paul Neagu's oversize original art (Box 130)
  - Jack Micheline materials (Box 194 (16x20))
  - General museum and exhibit posters, serials, etc. (Box 194 (16x20))
  - Various artist posters, prints, advertisements (Box 194 (16x20))
  - Posters from Kristine Stiles events and lectures (Box 194 (16x20))
  - Conventia Democratica din Romania advertisements (Box 194 (16x20))
  - Hermann Nitsch materials (Box 194 (16x20))
  - Dan and Lia Perjovschi newspapers, exhibit announcements, and other materials (Box 194 (16x20))
  - Enzo Cucchi album, 1983 (Box 195 (20x24))
  - Jack Micheline original art (Box 195 (20x24))
  - Jack Hirshman original art (Box 195 (20x24))
  - Original art, various artists
    - Menachen Kadishna drawings, 1996 (Box 195 (20x24))
    - Rudolf Schwartzkogler (Box 195 (20x24))
    - Doina Simionescu (Box 195 (20x24))
    - Suzanne Mailloux artist collage, 1978 (Box 195 (20x24))
    - Other unlabeled artwork (Box 195 (20x24))
  - Al Hansen materials (Box 195 (20x24))
  - General posters and materials (Box 195 (20x24))
  - Carolee Schneemann materials (Box 195 (20x24))
  - Roger Herman materials (Box 195 (20x24))
  - Hans Wanders exhibit poster (Box 195 (20x24))
  - Bruce Conner exhibit posters (Box 195 (20x24))
  - Original artwork and posters (various artists) (Box 206)
  - Posters (exhibits, advertisements, etc.) (Oversize-folder 1 (24x30))
  - Posters (exhibits, advertisements, etc.) (Oversize-folder 2 (32x40))
  - Original artwork (various artists) and posters (exhibits, advertisements, etc.) (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Original artwork (various artists) and posters (exhibits, advertisements, etc.) (Oversize-folder 4)
  - Posters (exhibits, advertisements, etc.) (Oversize-folder 5)
    Includes Jean Toche, Club Foot, and Dan Perjovschi exhibit posters.
  - Jean Toche: Oversize photographic works (Tube 1-12)